https://www.homeworksolutions.com/privacy-policy/

Knowledge Center
Why HomeWork Solutions?
Knowledge Center
Why HomeWork Solutions?
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for homeworksolutions.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order or place an order on your behalf.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (800) 626-4829 or via email.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
Sharing
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Remarketing
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Homework Solutions website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
Learn how to opt-out of ads.
Refer a Friend
$25 discount on new client set-up!
Free E-book
Guide to Household Payroll
Free Tip Sheet
Nanny Tax Quick Facts
Wonderful service staffed by nice people who enjoy dealing professionally with all-to-often less than thrilling payroll taxes. HomeWork Solutions provides a cost-effective service which delivers ... peace of mind with a smile.— Charles H., New York, NY
Your life is busy enough. Go ahead, simplify!
We would be delighted to help.
Services & Pricing Begin Enrollment
Still have questions? 1-800-626-4829
Contact Us
About Us HomeWork Solutions specializes in providing household employers and their tax preparers real solutions for nanny tax compliance. We are nationally recognized experts in the field of household employment taxes, regularly consulted by media such as the New York Times and Wall Street Journal.
From Our Blog
Unemployment Benefits and Taxes: Avoiding a Surprise Tax Bill Getting Health Insurance Coverage - My Head is Spinning, Where Do I Start? How to Respond When Your Nanny Goes Above and Beyond Helping Children with the Emotional Impacts of COVID-19
Quick Links
Service Plans & Pricing
Partner Program
Knowledge Center
Contact Us
Sitemap
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
HomeWork Solutions, Inc.
2 Pidgeon Hill Drive
Suite 300
Sterling,
VA
1-800-626-4829
(703) 404-8155
info@homeworksolutions.com
© 2020 HomeWork Solutions, Inc.. All Rights Reserved
FREE Updates & Tools
FREE Updates & Tools
Sign up with HomeWork Solutions today for valuable resources only available to our subscribers.
Receive industry related news and updates though our blog.
Access our FREE payroll tax calculators.
Access special offers & downloads.
I understand that I am registering for access to HWS. I grant HWS permission to contact me via email regarding household payroll and tax services they offer.
All fields are required.
7ads6x98y
